singapore2010.sg 2010-11-30

# Privacy Policy

_**1\. What information do we collect, and how do we collect it?**_

When you visit the Site, our web servers automatically collect certain data that your web browser sends whenever you visit any website, such as your IP (Internet Protocol) address and information relating to which pages have been viewed (e.g. using cookies as described further below).

When you use the Site, we collect information voluntarily submitted by you (e.g. via online or offline registration forms), such as your email address and any other contact details submitted by you and any optional services selected by you (e.g. whether you have chosen to receive future communications from us).

If you contact us, we may keep a record of that correspondence and, if so, shall treat that as PII.

In the course of using the Site as a registered user, you may choose to upload or post private information on public areas of the Site in the form of content and accompanying information. Any such content or accompanying information is not considered PII that is subject to this Privacy Policy.

_**2\. Information provided to us by children**_

We are committed to protecting the online privacy of children under the age of 18. We encourage parents and guardians to monitor their children's use of the internet. Where a child is providing us with PII, it is the responsibility of each parent or guardian to supervise them.

_**3\. How do we use your private information?**_

You agree that we may use your private information for the following purposes:

a.    We may use it to operate the features of the Site and to allow you, when you choose to do so, to participate in features available only to registered users or interactive features of the Site.

b.    We may use it, where you have consented to be contacted for such purposes, for the provision by us or by selected third parties of relevant information, products and/or services in which we think you may be interested.

c.    When you sign up to take part in a Singapore 2010 programme or initiative (e.g. our Singapore 2010 volunteer programme) or any Singapore 2010 business or cultural network that we may operate from time to time, or to receive online and/or email communications (e.g. newsletters or business e-alerts) or text communications (e.g. communications enabled via the Site between us and users of mobile telephones or other portable devices), we may use the information that you provide to maintain appropriate databases and otherwise to operate and facilitate such programmes, networks and communications.

d.    We may from time to time operate online job application systems via the Site. If you submit such an application, we may process the information provided by you for the purpose of considering the application.

e.    We may use anonymous information (i.e. other than PII), like your IP address, to compile statistics, to assess the usage of the Site and to customise the Site's content, lay-out and services. This will allow us to improve the Site and the services provided through it.

f.    We may provide your private information to any third party that administers any facility, service or promotion operated via the Site on our behalf to enable such third party to administer that facility, service or promotion properly.

g.    We may disclose your private information to any statutory body that may be established in connection with the Singapore 2010 Youth Olympic Games.

h.    The data that we collect from you may be transferred to, and stored at, a destination outside Singapore for processing by staff operating outside Singapore who work for us or for any other official SYOGOC affiliates. If you submit PII, you specifically consent by doing so to such transfer, storing or processing. We shall endeavour to ensure that your data is treated securely and in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

i.    We may transfer your private information in the event of a transfer of ownership of the Site or of SYOGOC.

j.    Apart from the purposes described above, we shall only use the private information that you provide to us for the purposes described at the point of collection or for purposes that are otherwise legally permitted.

_**4\. Cookies**_

The Site uses cookies. A cookie is a small file containing an identity code. Your computer accepts the cookie and stores it. When you next visit the Site, the code is retrieved, allowing an individual visitor or computer to be recognised.

Cookies are used for a variety of purposes, including providing personalised web pages and recognising your choice of language. Cookies do not cause harm to your computer, but, if you wish to stop your computer accepting cookies, go to the help section of your internet browser (e.g. Internet Explorer or Firefox), where you will find information on how to do this.

_**5\. Internet awareness**_

Whenever you voluntarily post PII in public areas of the Site, you should be aware that such information can be accessed by the public and may in turn be used by others to send you unsolicited communications. Please exercise discretion in deciding what information you provide.

_**6\. Other websites**_

The Site may contain links to other websites which are outside our control and are not covered by the terms of this Privacy Policy. If you access other websites using the links provided, the operators of those websites may collect information from you which will be used by them in accordance with their privacy policy, which may differ from ours.

_**7\. Security of your private information**_

Once we have received your private information, we shall endeavour to protect it by using physical, managerial and technical procedures and security features to try to prevent unauthorised access to it.

We cannot, however, guarantee the security of any private information provided to us in an email or in online form while it is being transmitted to us, as the internet is a potentially non-secure method of information transfer. Any such transmission is at your own risk.

We do not accept any responsibility for any loss, disruption or damage to your data or your computer system which may occur while using interactive features of the Site.

As best practice, we also strongly recommend that you regularly run an anti-virus software on all material downloaded from the internet.

_**8\. Updating your information and opting out**_

You may change your email address or name or cancel your registration for services provided via the Site at any time. Either navigate to the relevant section of the Site or click on the option to change your details or unsubscribe, or click on the relevant link in any email (or other electronic communication) sent by us to you.

_**9\. Updates to this Privacy Policy**_

If we update or otherwise change this Privacy Policy, we shall post the changes on this page and indicate at the top of this page when this Privacy Policy was last updated. Your continued use of the Site indicates your agreement to any such changes.

_**10\. Language**_

Please note that this Privacy Policy and Term of Use displayed on the Site ("Privacy Documents") have been drawn up in the English language and shall be interpreted in the English language.

Where any of the Privacy Documents (or any part of such Privacy Document) is translated into any language in addition to English and there is any conflict in meaning between the English-language version and such translated version, the English-language version shall prevail in all respects.
